http://calinjuryblog.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy Privacy Policy
California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog™ Privacy Policy: Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
This notice applies to all information collected from or submitted to the California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog Web site located at www.calinjuryblog.com, collectively referred to here as “our Web site.” Other California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog Web sites may operate under their own privacy notices.
Our Web site is not set up to automatically collect personally-identifiable information from visitors to our Web site. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our Web site. The server information is used only for internal purposes by our technical support staff. Our Web site does track certain non-personally-identifiable information about the visits to our Web site. For example, we compile aggregate statistics that show the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Web site and its individual pages. These aggregated statistics are used internally to improve our Web site and for product development and marketing purposes generally. The aggregated non-personal statistics may also be provided to advertisers and other third parties for certain purposes, but again, the statistics contain no personally-identifiable information and cannot be used to gather such information.
In a few areas on our Web site, we may ask you to provide personally-identifiable information that will enable us to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information, materials and services available from our Web site; to enable us to enhance your site visit; to assist you with customer service or technical support issues; to follow up with you after your visit; or to otherwise support your customer relationship with California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog. Your provision of this information and participation in the areas that require it is completely optional. You may decide not to provide the information and not to visit or access the areas that require it.
For example, we may request such information from you when you:
1. Log-on to certain areas of our Web site that require your user name and password as a condition to gaining access to the information, materials or services in that area.
2. Register or sign-up to subscribe to a service.
3. Subscribe to a newsletter or ask to be added to our mailing lists for other products or services.
4. Place an order for a product or service.
5. Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer.
6. Provide feedback in an online survey.
In each of the instances above, we typically ask for some or all of the following information: your name, e-mail address, phone number, mailing address, the type of business you are in, product preference information, any applicable identification number or password that we may require, as well as other similar information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain other information, materials and services. In the case of mailed materials, you will be able to “unsubscribe” to these mailings at any time.
California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog uses your personal information only for specific purposes. The personal information you provide to us when using our Web site — such as your name, postal or e-mail address or telephone number — will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog. It also may be used to notify you of special offers, updated information and new products and services from California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog.
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog, and/or other 3rd party advertisers.
Other unique circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties, such as in connection with a business divestiture or dissolution where all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information) are sold, or if disclosure is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.
You can opt-out of receiving further marketing materials from California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog at any time. We may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog (or agents or contractors working on behalf of California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog and under confidentiality agreements) are authorized to send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, you can tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time, you can opt-out of receiving further marketing materials from California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog by sending by clicking here and requesting to opt out.
Our Web site may make directories, chat rooms, forums, message boards and other interactive features available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas is not protected as confidential and becomes public information. You are solely responsible and should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information in these areas.
To prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
You can request a copy of the personally-identifiable information that California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog has collected about you via the Internet by contacting our Information Privacy Manager at the address below. You can also have factual inaccuracies in this information corrected by contacting this same person.
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write or e-mail us at the following address:
California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog
Law Offices of Norman Gregory Fernandez
9909 Topanga Canyon Blvd. #188
Chatsworth, CA 91311
E-mail: Law@norman-law.com
December 21, 2010
Privacy Policy Privacy Policy
California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog™ Privacy Policy: Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
This notice applies to all information collected from or submitted to the California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog Web site located at www.calinjuryblog.com, collectively referred to here as “our Web site.” Other California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog Web sites may operate under their own privacy notices.
Our Web site is not set up to automatically collect personally-identifiable information from visitors to our Web site. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our Web site. The server information is used only for internal purposes by our technical support staff. Our Web site does track certain non-personally-identifiable information about the visits to our Web site. For example, we compile aggregate statistics that show the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Web site and its individual pages. These aggregated statistics are used internally to improve our Web site and for product development and marketing purposes generally. The aggregated non-personal statistics may also be provided to advertisers and other third parties for certain purposes, but again, the statistics contain no personally-identifiable information and cannot be used to gather such information.
In a few areas on our Web site, we may ask you to provide personally-identifiable information that will enable us to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information, materials and services available from our Web site; to enable us to enhance your site visit; to assist you with customer service or technical support issues; to follow up with you after your visit; or to otherwise support your customer relationship with California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog. Your provision of this information and participation in the areas that require it is completely optional. You may decide not to provide the information and not to visit or access the areas that require it.
For example, we may request such information from you when you:
1. Log-on to certain areas of our Web site that require your user name and password as a condition to gaining access to the information, materials or services in that area.
2. Register or sign-up to subscribe to a service.
3. Subscribe to a newsletter or ask to be added to our mailing lists for other products or services.
4. Place an order for a product or service.
5. Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer.
6. Provide feedback in an online survey.
In each of the instances above, we typically ask for some or all of the following information: your name, e-mail address, phone number, mailing address, the type of business you are in, product preference information, any applicable identification number or password that we may require, as well as other similar information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain other information, materials and services. In the case of mailed materials, you will be able to “unsubscribe” to these mailings at any time.
California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog uses your personal information only for specific purposes. The personal information you provide to us when using our Web site — such as your name, postal or e-mail address or telephone number — will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog. It also may be used to notify you of special offers, updated information and new products and services from California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog.
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog, and/or other 3rd party advertisers.
Other unique circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties, such as in connection with a business divestiture or dissolution where all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information) are sold, or if disclosure is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.
You can opt-out of receiving further marketing materials from California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog at any time. We may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog (or agents or contractors working on behalf of California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog and under confidentiality agreements) are authorized to send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, you can tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time, you can opt-out of receiving further marketing materials from California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog by sending by clicking here and requesting to opt out.
Our Web site may make directories, chat rooms, forums, message boards and other interactive features available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas is not protected as confidential and becomes public information. You are solely responsible and should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information in these areas.
To prevent unauthorized access to your personal information, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
You can request a copy of the personally-identifiable information that California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog has collected about you via the Internet by contacting our Information Privacy Manager at the address below. You can also have factual inaccuracies in this information corrected by contacting this same person.
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write or e-mail us at the following address:
California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog
Law Offices of Norman Gregory Fernandez
9909 Topanga Canyon Blvd. #188
Chatsworth, CA 91311
E-mail: Law@norman-law.com
December 21, 2010
MORE INFORMATION ABOUT OUR LAW FIRM The California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog is published by California Personal Injury Attorney Norman Gregory Fernandez, Esq.
The Law Offices of Norman Gregory Fernandez & Associates are Personal Injury Attorney's who handle personal injury cases all over the State of California.
We are experts in dealing with Personal Injury cases.
Our Personal Injury Law Firm handles cases all over California inluding: 29 Palms, Adelanto, Agoura Hills. Alameda, Albany, Alhambra, Aliso Viejo, Alturas, Amador City, American Canyon, Anaheim, Anderson, Angels Camp, Antioch, Apple Valley, Arcadia, Arcata, Arroyo Grande, Artesia, Arvin, Atascadero, Atherton, Atwater, Auburn, Avalon, Avenal, Azusa, Bakersfield, Baldwin Park, Banning, Barstow, Beaumont, Bell, Bell Gardens, Bellflower, Belmont, Belvedere, Benicia, Berkeley, Beverly Hills, Big Bear Lake, Biggs, Bishop, Blue Lake, Blythe, Bradbury, Brawley, Brea, Brentwood, Brisbane, Buellton, Buena Park, Burbank, Burlingame, Calabasas, Calexico, California City, Calimesa, Calipatria, Calistoga, Camarillo, Canoga Park, Canyon Lake, Capitola, Carlsbad, Carmel-by-the-Sea, Carpinteria, Carson, Cathedral City, Century City, Ceres, Cerritos, Chatsworth, Chico, Chino, Chino Hills, Chowchilla, Chula Vista, Citrus Heights, Claremont, Clayton, Clearlake, Cloverdale, Clovis, Coachella, Coalinga, Colfax, Colma, Colton, Colusa, City of Commerce, Commerce, City of Industry, Compton, Concord, Corcoran, Corning, Corona, Corona Del Mar, Coronado, Corte Madera, Costa Mesa, Cotati, Covina, Crescent City, Cudahy, Culver City, Cupertino, Cypress, Daly City, Dana Point, Danville, Davis, Del Mar, Del Rey Oaks, Delano, Desert Hot Springs, Diamond Bar, Dinuba, Dixon, Dorris, Dos Palos, Downey, Duarte, Dublin, Dunsmuir, East Los Angeles, East Palo Alto, El Cajon, El Centro, El Cerrito, El Monte, El Segundo, Elk Grove, Emeryville, Encinitas, Escalon, Escondido, Etna, Eureka, Exeter, Fairfax, Fairfield, Farmersville, Ferndale, Fillmore, Firebaugh, Folsom, Fontana, Fort Bragg, Fort Jones, Fortuna, Foster City, Fountain Valley, Fowler, Fremont, Fresno, Fullerton, Galt, Garden Grove, Gardena, Gilroy, Glendale, Glendora, Goleta, Gonzales, Grand Terrace, Grass Valley, Greenfield, Gridley, Grover Beach, Guadalupe, Gustine, Half Moon Bay, Hanford, Hawaiian Gardens, Hawthorne, Hayward, Healdsburg, Hemet, Hercules, Hermosa Beach, Hesperia, Hidden Hills, Highland, Hillsborough, Hollister, Hollywood, Holtville, Hughson, Huntington Beach, Huntington Park, Huron, Imperial, Imperial Beach, Indian Wells, Indio, Industry, Inglewood, Ione, Irvine, Irwindale, Isleton, Jackson, Kerman, King City, Kingsburg, La Canada Flintridge, La Habra, La Habra Heights, La Mesa, La Mirada, La Palma, La Puente, La Quinta, La Verne, Lafayette, Laguna Beach, Laguna Hills, Laguna Niguel, Laguna Woods, Lake Elsinore, Lake Forest, Lakeport, Lakewood, Lancaster, Larkspur, Lathrop, Lawndale, Lemon Grove, Lemoore, Lincoln, Lindsay, Live Oak, Livermore, Livingston, Lodi, Loma Linda, Lomita, Lompoc, Long Beach, Loomis, Los Alamitos, Los Altos, Los Altos Hills, Los Angeles, Los Banos, Los Gatos, Loyalton, Lynwood, Madera, Malibu, Mammoth Lakes, Manhattan Beach, Manteca, Maricopa, Marina, Martinez, Marysville, Maywood, McFarland, Mendota, Menlo Park, Menifee, Merced, Mill Valley, Millbrae, Milpitas, Mission Viejo, Modesto, Monrovia, Montague, Montclair, Monte Sereno, Montebello, Monterey, Monterey Park, Moorpark, Moraga, Moreno Valley, Morgan Hill, Morro Bay, Mount Shasta, Mountain View, Murrieta, Napa, National City, Needles, Nevada City, Newark, Newman, Newport Beach, North Hills, North Hollywood, Norco, Northridge, Norwalk, Novato, Oakdale, Oakland, Oakley, Oceanside, Ojai, Ontario, Orange, Orange Cove, Orinda, Orland, Oroville, Oxnard, Pacific Grove, Pacifica, Palm Desert, Palm Springs, Palmdale, Palo Alto, Palos Verdes Estates, Paradise, Paramount, Parlier, Pasadena, Paso Robles, Patterson, Perris, Petaluma, Pico Rivera, Piedmont, Pinole, Pismo Beach, Pittsburg, Placentia, Placerville, Pleasant Hill, Pleasanton, Plymouth, Point Arena, Pomona, Port Hueneme, Porterville, Portola, Portola Valley, Poway, Rancho Cordova, Rancho Cucamonga, Rancho Mirage, Rancho Palos Verdes, Rancho Santa Margarita, Red Bluff, Redding, Redlands, Redondo Beach, Redwood City, Reedley, Reseda, Rialto, Richmond, Ridgecrest, Rio Dell, Rio Vista, Ripon, Riverbank, Riverside, Rocklin, Rohnert Park, Rolling Hills, Rolling Hills Estates, Rosemead, Roseville, Ross, Sacramento, Salinas, San Anselmo, San Bernardino, San Bruno, San Buenaventura, San Carlos, San Clemente, San Diego, San Dimas, San Fernando, San Fernando Valley, San Francisco, San Gabriel, San Gabriel Valley, San Jacinto, San Joaquin, San Jose, San Juan Bautista, San Juan Capistrano, San Leandro, San Luis Obispo, San Marcos, San Marino, San Mateo, San Pablo, San Rafael, San Ramon, Sand City, Sanger, Santa Ana, Santa Barbara, Santa Clara, Santa Clarita, Santa Cruz, Santa Fe Springs, Santa Maria, Santa Monica, Santa Paula, Santa Rosa, Santee, Saratoga, Sausalito, Scotts Valley, Seal Beach, Seaside, Sebastopol, Selma, Shafter, Shasta Lake, Sierra Madre, Signal Hill, Simi Valley, Solana Beach, Soledad, Solvang, Sonoma, Sonora, South El Monte, South Gate, South Lake Tahoe, South Los Angeles, South Pasadena, South San Francisco, St. Helena, Stanton, Stockton, Studio City, Suisun City, Sunnyvale, Susanville, Sutter Creek, Taft, Tarzana, Tehachapi, Tehama, Temecula, Temple City, Thousand Oaks, Tiburon, Torrance, Tracy, Trinidad, Truckee, Tulare, Tulelake, Toluca Lake, Turlock, Tustin, Twentynine Palms, Ukiah, Union City, Upland, Vallejo, Valley Village, Van Nuys, Ventura, Vernon, Victorville, Villa Park, Visalia, Vista, Walnut, Walnut Creek, Wasco, Waterford, Watsonville, Weed, West Covina, West Hills, West Hollywood, West Sacramento, West Carson, West Los Angeles, Westlake Village, Westminster, Westmorland, Wheatland, Whittier, Williams, Willits, Willows, Windsor, Winnetka, Winters, Woodlake, Woodland, Woodland Hills, Woodside, Yorba Linda, Yountville, Yreka, Yuba City, Yucaipa, Yucca Valley, Alameda County, Alpine County, Amador County, Butte County, Calaveras County, Colusa County, Contra Costa County, Del Norte County, El Dorado County, Fresno County, Glenn County, Humboldt County, Imperial County, Inyo County, Kern County, Kings County, Lake County, Lassen County, Los Angeles County, Madera County, Marin County, Mariposa County, Mendocino County, Merced County, Modoc County, Mono County, Monterey County, Napa County, Nevada County, Orange County, Placer County, Plumas County, Riverside County, Sacramento County, San Benito County, San Bernardino County, San Diego County, San Francisco County, San Joaquin County, San Luis Obispo County, San Mateo County, Santa Barbara County, Santa Clara County, Santa Cruz County, Shasta County, and Sierra County.
Go To TopAdministration LoginLaw Offices of Norman Gregory Fernandez & Associates - Copyright © 2020 California Personal Injury Lawyer Blog | Contact Us | Privacy Policy | Legal Disclaimer
